In this video, I will show you how to configure device enrollment manager.
So how do you actually configure device enrollment manager and who is the device enrollment
manager?
So to configure device enrollment manager, what you need to do is to go to devices.
And here we have device onboarding, so click enrollment, and here you can see we have the
device enrollment manager.
Both as the fall, who is the device enrollment manager?
According to Microsoft, a device enrollment manager is a non-abnestrator user who can
enroll devices in Microsoft Intune.
And also, a device enrollment manager are useful to have when you need to enroll and prepare
a lot of devices for your company.
Let me give you an example.
So people who are giving the opportunity to become a device enrollment manager can enroll
a managed up to 1,000 devices while a non-standard user or a user who is not a member of
the device enrollment manager can only enroll or manage 15 devices.
So it means you are a standard user can only manage 15 devices.
So in device enrollment manager, click add, and here you need to add the user accounts.
For example, you can see we have a Simon will now be just like add, will now be the device
enrollment manager.
Which means that this user can enroll up to 15 devices, up to a 1,000 devices, 15 is for
users who are being known, enrollment manager.
So we can't really just click the 3D dots here and then delete this user.
If we don't want the user to become a member of the DEM.
So this is how you add a user to become a member of the device enrollment manager or
Shorts for D-E-M